[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If youre a butterfingers and in your haste to get started on the daily chores you drop your breakfast toast, is it more likely to fall with butter side down?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This perennial herb from the mint family, that grows in wet soil, comes in two forms, a creeping variety and a more upright one.", "correct_answer": "Pennyroyal", "incorrect_answers": ["Water Lily", "Sassafras", "Cannabis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1984 movie starring Val Kilmer takes jabs at cold war spy thrillers and Elvis musicals.", "correct_answer": "Top Secret", "incorrect_answers": ["Hot Shots", "Real Genius", "UHF"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For what purpose were the WALL-E robots designed in the 2008 computer-animated science fiction movie WALL-E?", "correct_answer": "To clean up the planet", "incorrect_answers": ["To build spaceships", "To take care of human babies", "To make food for mankind"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do we call a triangle that has three unequal sides?", "correct_answer": "scalene", "incorrect_answers": ["heronian", "equilateral", "isosceles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the 2001 romantic comedy film that contains this quote: Is that a Members Only jacket? So what are you, the last member?", "correct_answer": "Shallow Hal", "incorrect_answers": ["The Breakfast Club", "Lethal Weapon", "Old School"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The jaguar is the national animal of which of the following countries?", "correct_answer": "Brasil", "incorrect_answers": ["Nicaragua", "Peru", "Costa Rica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long does it take for moonlight to reach the Earth?", "correct_answer": "Less than 3 seconds", "incorrect_answers": ["About 8 minutes", "About 3 minutes", "About 30 seconds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chris Tucker makes a cameo appearance in the film Next Friday.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Back to the Future, Doc Brown invented this device, which in his words is what makes time travel possible.", "correct_answer": "flux capacitor", "incorrect_answers": ["transference capacitor", "jauntinator", "transcendental tripometer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Actor Dax Shepard appeared in the TV series Robot Chicken.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What bird can be associated with the infectious disease Varicella?", "correct_answer": "Chicken", "incorrect_answers": ["Crane", "Hen", "Blue jay"]}]